(Leonard:)Sheldon, why didn't you tell me?
(Sheldon:)My bad.
I did send a gift from both of us.
(Beverley:)She's a remarkable girl. The youngest
appeals-court judge in New Jersey...
(Beverley:)...and a two-time
Olympic bronze medalist.
(Leonard:)You must be very happy.
(Beverley:)Why? I'm not marrying her.
(Beverley:)So how about you?
Are you seeing anyone interesting?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not sure
about interesting, but--
(Leonard:)-Not the time, Sheldon.
-Very well.
(Sheldon:)Shall we switch topics
to Isaac Newton v. Gottfried Leibniz?
(Beverley:)It's all right, Sheldon.
(Beverley:)I will just pretend that Leonard's
not withholding information.
(Beverley:)Although, I will point out, Leonard,
that I am a trained psychiatrist...
(Beverley:)...and you are exhibiting
the same secretive behavioral tics...
(Beverley:)...that accompanied
your learning to masturbate.
Isn’t she brilliant, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)How I envy you.
(Beverley:)So, Howard, have you and Rajesh
finally summoned the courage...
(Beverley:)...to express your latent
homosexual feelings towards one another?